mcbreo.com 2012-04-04

# Privacy Policy | MCB Michaelson, Connor, & Boul

### Our Privacy Policy

Michaelson, Connor, and Boul (MCB) respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.

### Information Collected

If you request or submit information to us by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "contact" form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.

### Information Collected by Others

This notice addresses only the policy of Michaelson, Connor, and Boul's website and not sites that users access via links from our site. MCB is not responsible for the information collection policies neither of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.

### Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information

If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an e-mail with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.

### Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information

MCB may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

### Periodic Policy Changes

Please note that MCB reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.

This policy statement is made in the name of company name and is effective as of January 1, 2010. This statement does not create an agreement between MCB and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.

### Trademarks and Usage

Trademarks and copyrights when specified in content of this website remain the property of their respective owners. Trademarks and other legally protected materials may not be duplicated, altered of repeated in any way without the express written permission of the owners.
